datingbuzz.co.za 2016-12-31

# DatingBuzz South Africa - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

Last Modified: 30 September 2013

For us, privacy is what it's all about. Sure we've got great technology, technically superior software and so on, but what really counts is our ability to provide our members with a safe, secure and private environment.

##### 1\. Information Collected

When you register as a member and set up a profile certain information is required. This includes personally identifiable information such as your name and email address. This information is stored on our systems, but NO personally identifiable information is ever displayed in your public profile or included in any communication between members sent via the site.

##### 2\. Updating Your Information

You can freely update all of your personal information including username, email address, location, password and all profile details. We encourage you to keep your details up to date.

##### 3\. Your Password

It is vital that you keep your password safe to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information. If you believe that your password has been compromised for any reason please CHANGE it immediately.

##### 4\. Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that allows us to recognise your computer from one page access to the next. We use only session cookies which are designed not to be permanent or persistent. The session cookie is designed so that, once you close your browser, the cookie will simply terminate. If you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may still use some, but not all, portions of our site. For example, the login process and all member functionality requires that your browser accept cookies. We recommend closing browsers on shared computers after use.

##### 5\. Deleting Your Information

You have the option to delete your profile. Please note that this permanently deletes all your information. No data will remain on our systems with the exception of personal correspondence or support enquiries sent to us, which may be stored on file.

##### 6\. Personal Correspondence

Correspondence sent to us including emails and letters will be stored on file with access limited to our authorised staff members.

##### 7\. Disclosure of Your Information

  * We will not disclose any of your information without your permission.
  * We will not supply any member's details to any other member - please don't even ask us.
  * We will not sell or rent or give your information to any third party.
  * We will only disclose your information if legally obligated to do so by a statutory authority with the appropriate jurisdiction.

##### 8\. No Spam Policy

No Spam, not now, not ever! You will receive emails from us and you may receive anonymous emails from other members. However, we will never supply, sell or rent your email address to any third party.

##### 9\. Internal Use of Information

We may internally use your information to improve our services, analyse site usage, optimise content, etc. This will only be conducted by authorised staff members. We may use personally identifiable information to troubleshoot problems and implement our terms and conditions.

##### 10\. Tell a Friend Services

Our site includes various 'tell a friend' services. Your friends will never receive unsolicited email from us and, once your 'tell a friend' email is sent, they will never hear from us again unless they choose to become members themselves. You may not use the 'tell a friend' services to send spam.

##### 11\. Social Network Sharing

Our members and site visitors have the option to share a profile they like with their friends on social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, etc. We will never disclose any personal details supplied by members that are not publicly displayed on the member's profile.

##### 12\. Security

Our technical team do their utmost to ensure the security of our systems. Internet Security is a complex topic and no system can be considered 100% secure. Should a security breach occur we would endeavour to react as fast as possible to remedy the problem. However we cannot assume responsibility for member details compromised in the unlikely event of a security breach.

##### 13\. Signing up with Social Network Accounts

We provide a quick and easy method for members to join or log in with a social network account, e.g. Facebook. This is for the sole purpose of speeding up the join process and no references to or content about DatingBuzz South Africa will be posted to your social network account or timeline. Refer to the 'Social Network Sharing' section for occasions where you may give permission to post updates on your social network account or timeline.

##### 14\. Changes to This Policy

If we make material changes to our privacy policy, these changes will be posted to our privacy policy page. You should review this page regularly for updates.
